INÊS SIMÕES

Hi! My name is Inês (Portuguese pronunciation: i'nes). I'm 28 years old and have been working as a software developer for a few years now. In my free time I enjoy playing Minecraft and listening to podcasts (Soft Skills Engineering being my favorite at the moment). In the last couple of months I've also been learning French and React!



CONTACT

ines.csim@gmail.com

+44 7761 824051 / +351 935 889 881

in Inês Simões

inescsim

inescsim.com

SKILLS

Languages
Portuguese

English

French

Programming JavaScript Ruby Ruby on Rails React HTML/CSS Java Python Operating Systems Linux MacOS Windows

WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR

WORK HISTORY

May 2019 to Present♥ Haplo, London, UK

Product Lead for Ethics Monitor

Product lead for Ethics Monitor, which helps universities streamline the review of applications for ethical approval. During my time at Haplo I worked closely with new clients throughout the process of building their custom application, provided support for existing clients and worked alongside my colleagues to improve the product.

🛗 Sep 2018 to Jan 2019

♥ HYP, Portugal

Software Developer

Collaboration with The Loop Co to develop babyloop.pt, a platform to buy and sell used baby products (such as cribs, car seats, etc). Product built using Ruby on Rails.

Mar 2017 to Aug 2018

OneSource, Portugal

Junior Ruby Developer

Extension for SketchUp to optimize the structure of the building designed by the user as well as maintenance and building costs so as to render the optimal solution. SketchUp's API was used to assess any relevant information of the building so as to conclude about properties like number of floors (including underground), available floor space, etc and therefore the costs and optimization needed.

H Jul 2016 to Sep 2016

HYP, Portugal

Ruby on Rails Internship

Web application to pick movies to watch with friends, based on which movies everyone wants to watch.

EDUCATION

September 2012 - August 2017

Q University of Coimbra, Portugal

Bachelor's Degree, Informatics Engineering